Guide to the Group Research, Inc. Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XV: Audio/Visual Material
  - Subseries XV.2: Audio Reels (5 inch)
    - Church League of America Major Bundy Attack on IAD (Box 509)
    - Father Fenton Tapes 1&4 (Box 509)
    - Father Fenton Tapes 2&3 (Box 509)
    - Holmes, Lola Belle, Fort Wayne, Ind., June 1967 (Box 509)
    - John Birch Society (Box 509)
    - McIntire, Carl, 27 Nov. (Box 509)
    - National Strategy Information Center (Box 509)
    - Publius & Associates To Protect and To Serve, 1967 (Box 509)
    - Pyne, Joe: Jalie Boonn (Box 509)
    - Pyne, Joe: Dr. Anthony Burscaren. Am. Sec. Council-Y.A.F. (Box 509)
    - Pyne, Joe: Alan Stang & Mr. Teharina, 26 Oct. 1967 (Box 509)
    - Russelot on Lomax Show (Box 509)
    - Welch, Robert: Idaho Press Conference and Speech, 14-15 April 1967 (2) (Box 509)
    - Welch, Robert: Idaho Press Conference and Speech on Vietnam Part 2 (Box 509)
    - While Brave Men Die Soundtrack (Box 509)
    - Unidentified (4) (Box 509)
  - Subseries XV.3: Audio Reels (large)
    - Capell, Frank (Box 510)
    - Cardinal Mindszenty Foundation 3rd Leadership Conference, March 1965 (Box 510)
    - Christian Crusade for God and Country Convention Address by Tom Anderson, 1961 (Box 510)
    - Christian Crusade for God and Country Convention Address by Robert Welch (2), 1961 (Box 510)
    - Cross (Box 510)
    - Barry Farber Show 673 Tom Davis Part 1 (Box 510)
    - Barry Farber Show 674 Tom Davis Part 2 (Box 510)
    - Group Investigation Associates Interview with Three Minutemen Who Raided the Pacifist Camp, 24 Nov. 1968 (Box 510)
    - John Birch Society: Thirteenth Anniversary Dinner, 3 Dec. 1971 (Box 510)
    - Filmstrip: The Great Pretense: How to Finance Communism While Ostensibly Opposing It (Box 510)
    - Filmstrip: Subsidized Revolution: The War on Poverty (Box 510)
    - I.A.D. Annual Meeting, NYC, 13 May 1968 (Box 510)
    - Life Line, 28 Oct. (Box 510)
    - McIntire, Carl McIntire/Williams (Box 510)
    - McIntire, Carl McIntire/Manion, Jan. 7-9 (Box 510)
    - McIntire, Carl McIntire, 11 Aug. (Box 510)
    - McIntire, Carl McIntire/Harvey, 18 Aug. (Box 510)
    - McIntire, Carl McIntire, 26 Oct. (Box 510)
    - McIntire, Carl McIntire/Manion, 20-23 Dec. (Box 510)
    - McIntire, Carl McIntire Takeover: ACCC, 28 Oct. 1970 (Box 510)
    - Miller, 2 Aug. (Box 510)
    - Frank R. Barnett "National Priorities and National Defense" (Box 510)
    - Roy Godson "Youth Today: The Questioning Americans" (Box 510)
    - Harold K. Johnson "A Citizen-Soldier Speaks Out" (Box 510)
    - Lyman B. Kirkpatrick, Jr. "Soviet Espionage in the 70s" (Box 510)
    - Sven Kraemer "Southeast Asia and the U.S." (Box 510)
    - William C. Mott "America's Youth and Our Free Society" (Box 510)
    - Bonaro Wilkinson Overstreet "Communism in a Changing World" (Box 510)
    - Nquyen Van Tho "A Vietnam Look at the Vietnam War" (Box 510)
    - Frank N. Trager "Vietnam-Who's Winning?" (Box 510)
    - Leonid V. Vladimirov "Why I Chose to Defect to the West" (Box 510)
  - Subseries XV.4: Audio Reels (large)
    - New England Rally for God, Family, and Country: #6 Songs by Vera Vanderlaan; Laurence C. Baldauf, Jr., Reed Beson; Billy James Hargis, Robert D. Dilley, 1967 (Box 511)
    - #10: Mrs. Rose Martin, Gina O'Brien Manion; Dean Clarence Manion, Thomas J. Anderson, John Brown, William J. Grede, 1967 (Box 511)
    - #6 Dr. Medford Evans, General Edwin A. Walker; Billy James Hargis, Colonel Curtis B. Dall, 1968 (Box 511)
    - #7 Lt. Gov. Lester Maddox, Frank Garlock, 1973 (Box 511)
    - #10 A.B.J. Hammett, Hon. John G. Schmitz, 1973 (Box 511)
    - #13 Dr. Bob Jones, Tom Anderson, 1973 (Box 511)
    - Dr. Revilo Oliver, 28 Aug. 1964 (Box 511)
    - Only the Strong (Box 511)
    - Dan Smoot (Box 511)
    - Stang (Box 511)
    - U.S.I.A./V.O.A (Box 511)
    - Wallace, Gov. George, National Press Club, 6 Dec. 1971 (Box 511)
    - Welch, Robert Welch (Box 511)
    - Welch, Robert If You Want It Straight (Box 511)
    - Wyze, Cotton; Wyze, Hargis, 20-23 Feb & 24-25 Feb. (Box 511)
    - Unidentified (8) (Box 511)
- Series XVI: Manuscript Files on Audio/Visual Material
  - Subseries XVI.1: Audiovisual Information: Manuscripts
    - Dr. Peter Beter Monthly Audio Letter, 19 July 1976, 26 Oct. 1976 (Box 511)
    - John Birch Society Subsidized Revolution: The War on Poverty (Box 511)
    - Long, Hamilton A. Permit Communist-Conspirators to Be Teachers? (Box 511)
    - Spotlight: Station List, 16 Oct. 1964 (Box 511)
    - Text of Spotlights: #1 Rockefeller (Box 511)
    - #2 Minutemen (Box 511)
    - #3 Pleasantville (Box 511)
    - #4 Violence (Box 511)
    - #5 Welch on Welch (Box 511)
    - #6 News and Comment (Box 511)
    - #7 Religious Hokum (Box 511)
    - #8 Interlocking (Box 511)
    - #9 Who's the Target (Box 511)
    - #10 America's Future (Box 511)
    - #11 Courtneys (Box 511)
    - #12 Midlothian Violence (Box 511)
    - #13 Manion Forum (Box 511)
    - #14 Hazel Brannon Smith (Box 511)
    - #15 YAF (Box 511)
    - #16 Mitchell (Box 511)
    - # 17 You've Got to be Taught (Box 511)
    - # 18 Finances (Box 511)
  - Subseries XVI.2: Cassette Tapes
    - Pastor Sheldon Emry America's Promise: Warning of Judgment to Washington D.C. (Box 512)
    - Pastor Sheldon Emry America Needs a Christian Government! (Box 512)
    - Beter, Dr. Peter Dr. Peter Beter's Monthly Audio Letter, Nov. 1976 #18 (Box 512)
    - Citizens United for America Foundation The Inside Look, Dec. 1980 (Box 512)
    - Citizens United for America Foundation The Inside Look, Jan. 1981 (Box 512)
    - Dinsmore, Herman KJOY "Hotline", 8 Feb. 1970 (Box 512)
    - Falwell, Jerry Side 1: 23 Nov. 1980; 7 April 1981; 19 April 1981; 17 May 1981; 12 July 1981; 29 May 1981 (Box 512)
    - Falwell, Jerry Side 2: 29 March 1981; 28 Dec. 1980; 2 Aug. 1981; 11 Oct. 1981 (Box 512)
    - Gimpner, Rev. John "Wash. For Jesus", National Press Club, 4/23 (Box 512)
    - John Birch Society Annual Council Dinner [Nicholas Bovey, Robert Welch], 9 June 1973 (Box 512)
    - John Birch Society Annual Council Dinner [Jack McManus, William McIlhaney], 9 June 1973 (Box 512)
    - James Cox, [B.B.C.] Feature on Lyndon Larouche (Box 512)
    - Lewis, J.C. The Trilateral Commission (Box 512)
    - Radio America, 3 June 1985. (Box 512)
    - Cuomo, Joe Ronald Reagan and the Prophecy of Armageddon, WBAI, 1985 (Box 512)
    - Roberts, Col. Arch E. Land Control Laws: Do They Cancel Your Private Property Rights? (Box 512)
    - Town Talk, 11 & 25 Feb. 1974 (Box 512)
    - Welch, Robert What Is Communism, Gary Allen Communications (Box 512)
    - Welles, Orson In the Beginning (Box 512)
  - Subseries XVI.3: Film Strips
    - The Great Pretense: How to Finance Communism While Ostensibly Opposing It, John Birch Society (Box 512)
    - Subsidized Revolution: The War on Poverty, John Birch Society (Box 512)
    - Assasination, Publius & Associates, 1967 (Box 512)
    - To Protect and To Serve, Publius & Associates, 1967 (Box 512)
  - Subseries XVI.4: VHS
    - Falwell/Liberty University Ollie North: An American Hero. Ollie North's "Liberty Address,", 1988 (Box 512)
    - People for the American Way Six 60 Second Spots (Box 512)
  - Subseries XVI.5: L-500 VHS
    - People for the American Way Six 60 Second Spots (Box 512)
  - Subseries XVI.6: Card Files
    - Abortion (Box 512)
    - Audiovisual (Box 512)
    - Richard Viguerie Clients and Business (Box 512)
    - Herblock Cartoon from the Washington Post, Washington, D.C., 1962 (Box 727)
      [Inscribed]
    - Sullivan Bob Cartoon from the Worcester Telegraph & Gazette, Worcester, MA, 1980 (Box 727)
      [Signed]
    - "Barry Goldwater", [n.p.], [n.d.], (1 Book Jacket ) (Box 727)
    - Gersten Cartoon from Esquite, [New York], May 1992 (Box 727)
    - "Salute to the American Right", [New York], August 1962, (1 Photogrpah ) (Box 727)